<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>About on Jakub Kuzilek</title>
    <link>https://jakubkuzilek.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content in About on Jakub Kuzilek</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://jakubkuzilek.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://jakubkuzilek.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jakubkuzilek.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>About Me  I am Prague (CZ) based postdoc researcher focusing on Educational Data Mining and Learning Analytics. I am interested in machine learning, signal processing, and R. Let&amp;rsquo;s start scrolling and learn more.

I am postdoc researcher at Czech Technical University in Prague. Since completion of my Ph.D. in Biomedical Signal Processing using Blind Source Separation methods I am focusing on Educational Data Mining and Learning Analytics research. This switch was caused by professor Zdenek Zdrahal from Knowledge Media Institute (Open University) who invited me to work with him on Data Mining of student data in project OU Analyse.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://jakubkuzilek.github.io/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jakubkuzilek.github.io/contact/</guid>
      <description>Contact  Email: jakub.kuzilek@hu-berlin.de
Phone: +49 30 2093-41119
  Due to COVID-19 situation I am not usually in the office. Please, use e-mail for the queries. Mailing Address  Rudower Chaussee 25, Room 3.415
Berlin
Germany
  Social  Scholar Twitter LinkedIn  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>https://jakubkuzilek.github.io/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jakubkuzilek.github.io/publications/</guid>
      <description>Publications 2021 Kuzilek, J., Zdrahal, Z., &amp;amp; Fuglik, V. (2021). Student success prediction using student exam behaviour. Future Generation Computer Systems.
Clara Schumacher, &amp;amp; Jakub Kuzilek (2021). Perfect Match? Investigating Students’ Perceptions About Algorithmic Grouping in Higher Education. In Accepted for presentation at 2021 AECT International Convention.
Paaßen, B., et. al. (2021). Analyzing Student Success and Mistakes in Virtual Microscope Structure Search Tasks. In Proceedings of the 15th International Conference on Educational Data Mining (EDM 2021).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Research</title>
      <link>https://jakubkuzilek.github.io/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jakubkuzilek.github.io/research/</guid>
      <description>Research I am a senior postdoctoral researcher at Humbold-University of Berlin in Prof. Niels Pinkwart research group. At present, I am focusing on the research on collaborative learning with a particular focus on group interaction in online environments during the work on the assigned task. I am focusing on methods, which uncovers the behaviour leading to: 1) Successful finish of the task; 2) Identification of at-risk collaborative groups; 3) Automatic forming the collaborative groups.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teaching</title>
      <link>https://jakubkuzilek.github.io/teaching/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jakubkuzilek.github.io/teaching/</guid>
      <description>Teaching Here you can find current (most recent) information for students.
Individual projects Forschungsseminar des Lehrstuhls &amp;ldquo;Didaktik der Informatik | Informatik und Gesellschaft&amp;rdquo; Research seminar website
Students need to work on a small research topic (make a state-of-the-art, small project). Feel free to contact me, and we will work out a topic based on your interests and experience.
Past projects:
 Celina Loeper: Prediction of student success with Deep Learning  Forschungsseminar lectures R (2021-05-11)</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
