<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>learning-analytics on Jakub Kuzilek</title>
    <link>/tags/learning-analytics/</link>
    <description>Recent content in learning-analytics on Jakub Kuzilek</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2018 Jakub Kuzilek</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/learning-analytics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Student drop-out modelling using Virtual Learning Environment behaviour data</title>
      <link>/post/2018_04_12_student_behaviour_analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2018_04_12_student_behaviour_analysis/</guid>
      <description>This post is a companion for the short paper submitted to EC-TEL 2018 conference. It contains details of the whole study and some more information such as figures, which does not fit in to the paper. For the analysis we used Open University Learning Analytics dataset.
 This is draft version of companion, if you spot an error, typo or you have any comment, please let me know.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Student Analyse</title>
      <link>/project/student_analyse/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/student_analyse/</guid>
      <description>The project aims at the development of predictive modelling methods reflecting different views (levels) of student academic path and dependencies between „resources” student interacts with during the learning process. In addition, by investigating dependencies between „educational resources” we will develop methods for the analysis of student learning behaviour. All developed methods will be tested on real data provided by partner institutions - Open University and Faculty of Mechanical Engineering, CTU in Prague.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OU Analyse</title>
      <link>/project/ou_analyse_project/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2014 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/ou_analyse_project/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>